原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     木淺   Eunice
翻譯     Ethan-澤生
時間軸     少年派
校對     少年派
後期     8T
總監     somehacker  少年派
數個世紀來  聖殿騎士團
For centuries, the Order of the Knights Templar...
一直在尋找傳說中的伊甸蘋果
have searched for the mythical Apple of Eden.
他們相信其中蘊含的
They believe it contains not only
不僅是人類第一次違抗命令的種子
the seeds of man's first disobedience,
也是打開自由意志的鑰匙
but the key to the free will itself.
只要找到遺寶  破解它的秘密
If they find the relic and decode its secrets,
他們就將擁有控制所有自由思想的力量
they will have the power to control all freedom of thought.
刺客兄弟會  是他們唯一的阻礙
Only the brotherhood called the Assassins stands in their way...
西班牙  安達盧西亞  1492年
宗教裁判所終於將西班牙交給了聖殿騎士團
The Inquisition has finally delivered Spain to the Templars.
穆罕默德蘇丹和他的人還在格拉納達負隅頑抗
Sultan Muhammad and his people still hold out in Granada.
但如果能抓住他的兒子  他的小王子
But if his son, the prince, is captured,
他必將獻出城池  還有伊甸蘋果
he will surrender the city and the Apple of Eden.
你  阿圭拉·德·納哈
Do you, Aguilar de Nerha,
是否起誓在自由之戰中守護我們的刺客兄弟會
swear to honor our order in the fight for freedom?
為了人類抵抗聖殿騎士團的暴政
To defend mankind against Templars' tyranny,
守護自由意志
and preserve free will?
我起誓
I swear.
如果伊甸蘋果落入他們之手
If the Apple falls into their hands,
聖殿騎士團將毀滅一切阻礙
the Templars will destroy everything that stands in their way.
抗議  反對  自由思考是我們的權利
Protest, dissent, our right to think for ourselves.
向我起誓  哪怕犧牲你自己的
Swear to me that you will sacrifice your life
甚至這裏所有人的性命  也不會令其落入他們之手
and lives of everyone here to keep it from them.
遵命  師父
Yes, Mentor.
我們的生命不重要
Our lives are nothing.
伊甸蘋果才是一切
The Apple is everything.
雄鷹之靈  將守護我們的未來
The spirit of the Eagle, will watch over the future.
所有人都盲目追尋著真相時
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
謹記  一切皆虛
remember, nothing is true.
所有人都被道德或法律束縛時
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
謹記  無事不允
remember, everything is permitted.
我們在黑暗中侍奉光明
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們  是刺客
We are Assassins.
刺客信條
墨西哥  下加州  1986年
媽的
Shit!
媽媽
Mom?
爸爸
Dad?
你的生命不是你個人的  卡爾
Your blood is not your own, Cal.
他們找到我們了
They've found us.
要活在暗處
Live in the shadows.
走  快走
Go! Go now!
30年後
美國德州  亨茨維爾監獄
你是來拯救我的靈魂的
You're here to save my soul.
差不多吧
Something like that.
我
I...
我瞭解到今天是你生日
I understand it is your birthday.
是啊
Yeah.
生日派對正要開始呢
The party is just getting started.
坐下  你讓我緊張
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
主啊  洗刷我的罪孽
Lord, wash away my sin,
我將重新潔淨
and I will be clean, once again.
你不怎麼信《聖經》  是嗎
You're not much for the Bible, are you?
卡勒姆·林奇
Be it known that Callum Lynch
被判謀殺罪  將於今日
has been found guilty of capital murder
即2016年10月21日  執行死刑
and sentenced to die on this day, October 21st 2016.
囚犯有什麼遺言嗎
Does the prisoner wish to make a final statement?
請轉告我父親  就說我們地獄再見
Tell my father that I'll see him in hell.
我叫索菲婭·萊肯
My name is Dr. Sophia Rikkin.
昨晚6點整  你被執行死刑
At 6 P.M. yesterday evening, you were executed
並宣佈死亡
and pronounced dead.
現在  對這世上任何認識你或在乎你的人來說
And so far, as anyone in the world knows or cares,
你已經不存在了
you no longer exist.
你最好還是坐著
It's better you to sit.
我的眼睛...
My eyes...
你現在的感覺很正常  雖然不舒服
What are you feeling right now is normal and uncomfortable.
卡爾
Cal.
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.
你也要幫助我
And you're here to help me.
讓他走
Let him go.
別碰他
Don't touch him.
來啊  勇敢去做啊
Go ahead. Do it.
跳啊
Jump.
你在這裏不是囚犯  卡爾
You are not a prisoner here, Cal.
我是來保護你的
I'm here to protect you.
如果你認真聽我的話  慢慢你就會明白一切
If you listen to me, everything is going to make sense.
而且你得信任我
And you need to trust me.
我在哪兒
Where am I?
你在馬德里阿布斯泰戈基金會的康復區
You're in a rehabilitation wing of abstergo Foundation in Madrid,
一個致力於實現完美人類的私人機構
a private organization dedicated to the perfection of human kind.
有你的幫助  我們就能開闢新途徑
With your help, we can pioneer new ways
最終消除暴力
to eradicate violence.
我可以搞定的
I had this.
你父親命令帶他回去
Your father wants him in.
他是我的病人  這是我的項目
He's my patient. This is my program.
準備阿尼姆斯
Prepare the Animus.
-刺客之刃準備好了嗎  -就在這兒
- Are the blades prepared? - Right here.
-刺客之刃主人確定了嗎  -是阿圭拉的
- And we confirmed their provenance? - They belong to Aguilar.
是從他的墳墓找回的
We recovered them from his burial site.
這是什麼
What are these?
最後階段準備
Assume final preparations.
回溯坐標  1492年  安達盧西亞
Our regression, Andalusia, 1492.
完整記錄下來一切
Record everything.
機械臂準備完畢
Arms ready.
這是怎麼回事
What is this?
抱歉  卡爾  我也不喜歡用這種方式
I'm sorry, Cal, this is not the way I like to do things.
那就別這麼做
Then don't do it.
進行硬膜外麻醉注射
Insert epidural.
你到底想從我身上得到什麼
What do you want from me?
你的過去
Your past.
認真聽我說  卡爾
Listen to me carefully, Cal.
你即將進入阿尼姆斯
You're about to enter the Animus.
你將看到的  聽到的  感到的一切
What you are about to see, hear and feel,
都是一個已經死去五百年之人的記憶
are the memories of someone who has been dead for 500 years.
等等
Wait a minute.
你無法抵抗的  卡爾
You can't change what happens, Cal.
啟動掃瞄設備
Engage scanner.
狀態如何
Status?
掃瞄DNA鏈  正在搜索時間幀
Scanning DNA chains. Searching for time frame.
第一匹配記憶已鎖定
First memory match locked.
匹配DNA已識別
DNA match identified.
不要抵抗  卡爾
Stay with it, Cal.
嘗試同步
Attempt synchronization.
找到他了
We found him.
我們找到了阿圭拉
We found Aguilar.
同步達成
Synchronization achieved.
好了
There.
啟動回溯
Commence regression.
我們的任務是找到那孩子
Our mission is the boy.
是王子
It's the prince.
是誰家藏匿了這個孩子
Which household harbored the boy?
只有我
Only me.
其他人都不知道  沒人知道
Nobody else knew. Nobody.
絞死他的家人  讓他看著
Hang his family and make him watch.
燒掉整個村子
Burn the whole village.
有格拉納達王子做人質  他父親蘇丹
With the prince of Granada as captive, his father, Sultan,
將獻出叛軍城池
will surrender his rebellious city,
那是異教徒的最後避風港
the last safe haven for the infidels.
上帝將懲罰他們信奉的異教
God will punish his people's heresy.
西班牙終於要臣服於聖殿騎士團之統治
Finally Spain will be under one Templar rule.
跟著記憶走  卡爾
Stay with the memory, Cal.
阿圭拉  那孩子  阿圭拉  孩子
Aguilar! The boy, Aguilar! The boy!
阿圭拉  孩子
Aguilar, the boy!
把他拉回來
Pull him!
啟動復原
Commence rehabilitation.
進行系統檢查  記錄他的情況
Run a system's check, and log his condition.
你做得很好  卡爾
You did well, Cal.
回顧歷史  很明確的一點就是
Looking back it's clear that
世界歷史就是一部暴力史
a history of the world is history a violence.
去年的反社會行為
Last year the economic impact of
對經濟造成的損失高達9萬億美元
antisocial behavior was 9 trillion dollars.
我們認為現代人總會有一些暴力衝動
We believe that man today experiences a measure of aggression
但卻找不到合適的宣洩方式
for which he finds no acceptable outlets.
想像一下
Now imagine
如果這些代價  可以在別的地方得到管控...
if all these costs could be channeled elsewhere...
回溯進行得順利嗎
So regression went well?
就是林奇
Lynch is the one.
他是阿圭拉的直系後裔
Direct descendent of Aguilar.
一切都清晰了起來  這可是第一次
Everything was clear in there, for the first time.
我們共同的夢想是什麼
What do we all dream of?
就是一個更和平的世界
A more peaceful world.
你又盜用我的演講辭
I see you stole my lines again.
我只盜用最出色的人
I only steal from the best.
那件寶物呢
And the artifact?
伊甸蘋果  唾手可得
The Apple. It's within our grasp.
在裏面發生了什麼
What happened in there?
你為什麼將他拉回來了
Why did you pull him?
我必須如此
I had to.
我們要保護他的安全
We have to keep him healthy.
贏得他的信任
Earn his confidence.
我確信他能帶領我們找到寶物
And I know that will lead us to it.
對他狠點
Push him.
阿尼姆斯的運作方式不是這樣的
That's not how the Animus works.
好了
Here you go.
謝謝
Thank you.
1917年  盧瑟福分裂開了原子
1917 Rutherford splits the atom.
1953年  沃森和克裏克發現雙螺旋
1953 Watson and Crick find a double helix.
2016年  我的女兒
2016 my daughter,
找到了根除暴力的方法
finds the cure for violence.
你向來都比我聰明
You've always been brighter than me.
我要遲到了
I'm late.
我還得向長老會匯報
I have to report to the Elders.
弗朗西斯科·利茲的《宗教裁判所大法官》
Francisco Rizi's Grand Inquisition.
1492年
1492.
戰爭  宗教迫害
War, religious prosecution,
也是托爾克馬達法官及騎士團成員
and the closest Father Torquemada or any of our Order
尋找伊甸蘋果最接近成功的一次了
came to a finding the Apple of Eden.
你還好嗎  朋友
How are you, my friend?
很好
Well.
大人
Your Excellency.
下周  等長老們會面
Next week when the Elders meet,
我們會就是否中斷你的阿布斯泰戈項目進行投票
we shall vote to discontinue your Abstergo project.
我們覺得  每年給你的三十億資金
We feel that giving you 3 billion annually,
花在別處會有更大的用途
could be better spent elsewhere.
三十億相比...
Tri billion is nothing compared to...
我們勝利了
We've won.
人們已經不在乎他們的公民自由了
People are no longer care about their civil liberties,
他們只在乎自己的生活水平
they care about their standard of life.
現代世界已經拋棄自由這種理念了
The modern world has outgrown notions like freedom.
他們樂於盲從
They are content to follow.
只要自由意志尚存  威脅就依然存在
The threat remains while free will exists.
數個世紀以來  我們試圖通過宗教
For centuries we try with religion,
政治  以及現在的消費主義  來剷除異議
with politics and now consumerism to eliminate dissent.
現在難道不是時候嘗試科學辦法了嗎
Isn't it the time we gave a science a try?
我女兒比我們所有人都要更接近成功了
My daughter is closer than we've ever been.
你美麗的女兒怎麼樣了
How is your beautiful daughter?
她追蹤到了伊甸蘋果的守護者
She has traced protectors of the Apple.
在哪兒
Where?
安達盧西亞  1492年
Andalucia, 1492.
他們的後人呢
The descendents?
所有的後人都死光了
All the blood lines have died out.
只剩下一個
But one.
我們追蹤他的血脈到500年前
We've traced his back 500 years,
定位到刺客兄弟會身上
to the Assassin's Brotherhood.
幻覺  就是我們所謂的"血緣效應"
Hallucinations are what we call the "Bleeding effect."
回溯後的畫面
Images of your regression,
潛藏在你現在的視界裏
laying themselves over your present day field of vision.
如果你允許的話  我可以教你怎麼控制它們
If you allow me, I can teach you how to control them.
退下  我可以搞定
Stand down. I have this.
隨她去吧
Let her be.
那台機器  到底是什麼東西
What is it? The machine?
那是基因記憶機器
It's genetic memory.
通過使用阿尼姆斯
By using the Animus,
我們可以獲取祖先的記憶
we can relive lives of those who made us who we are.
我看到的情形  感覺很真實
What I saw in there, it felt real.
的確如此
It was.
在某種程度上是
In a way.
別跟我耍花招
Don't mess with me!
我現在感覺不一樣了
I feel different now.
為什麼這麼有攻擊性
Why the aggression?
我本就是個有攻擊性的人
I'm an aggressive person.
這是什麼監獄
What kind of prison is this?
這裏不是監獄  卡爾
It's not a prison, Cal.
只要你乖乖合作  就會瞭解到更多東西
You'll learn more if you cooperate.
放開我
Let me go.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
跟我來
Come with me.
林奇
1979年-現在
這是什麼東西
What is this?
對卡勒姆·林奇的擔憂加深
我知道關於你的一切  卡爾
I know everything about you, Cal.
黑幫突襲當地辦事處
林奇必死無疑
你的醫療數據  你的心理檔案
Your medical data, your psychological profile,
以及你MAO-A基因的變異
the mutations in your MAO-A gene.
我知道你在寄養家庭的事
I know about the foster homes.
在少管所的事
The juvenile homes.
你是遺傳和犯罪存在關聯的活生生的證據
You are a living proof of the link between heredity and crime.
你們是怎麼找到我的
How did you find me?
我們先找到了阿圭拉
We found Aguilar.
你被逮捕時  你的DNA被發現與他的相匹配
When you were arrested, your DNA matched his.
-阿圭拉是誰  -你的祖先
- Who is Aguilar? - Your ancestor.
他的家族祖上都是刺客
His family were Assassins.
他們被聖殿騎士團  托爾克馬達  和你看到的
They were burnt at the stake by the Templars,
那個黑衣騎士奧哈達綁在柱子上燒死了
Torquemada and the black knight you saw, Ojeda.
阿圭拉繼承了刺客大業
Aguilar took up the Assassins' cause.
你經常外出嗎
Do you go out much?
比你外出的時候多
More than you.
這裏的其他人呢  也都是實驗室裏的小白鼠嗎
And the others in here? Are they the lab rats too?
他們也是刺客  跟他們的祖先一樣都是殺手
They are Assassins, murderers like their ancestors.
跟你一樣  卡爾
Like you, Cal.
天生就具有暴力傾向
All born with predisposition to violence.
殺手
Murderer?
-你殺了那個人  -他是個皮條客
- You killed the man. - A pimp.
你會再次殺人嗎
Would you kill again?
幸福的一家人
Happy families.
她一定為你感到很驕傲
She must be very proud.
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
她被一名刺客殺死了
She was killed by an Assassin.
跟你母親的遭遇一樣
Like your mother.
抱歉
Sorry.
我父親殺了我母親
My old man killed my mother.
那讓你是什麼感覺
And how does that make you feel?
我想殺了他
Like killing him.
要麼我們讓這事影響我們一輩子
Either we let it to effect us for the rest of our lives,
要麼採取點措施
or we just do something about it.
你選擇了暴力  我選擇了科學
You turn to violence, I turn to science.
那是伊甸蘋果  卡爾
It's the Apple of Eden, Cal.
我相信它真的存在
I believe it exists.
《聖經》告訴我們
The Bible tells us
其中蘊含了人類第一次違抗命令的種子
it contained the seed of man's first disobedience.
但也有些人認為
But there are those of us who believe that
上帝  或某種古文明
God or some ancient civilization
給我們留下了一張指示圖
have left us a road map
幫助我們瞭解人為什麼會有暴力性
to understand why people are violent.
據稱伊甸蘋果最後一次出現是在阿圭拉手上
Aguilar was the last person known to have had it in his possession.
我們需要你查出他把那東西藏在哪兒了
We need you to find out where he hid it.
我以為我是來接受治療的
I thought I was here to be cured.
暴力就是一種疾病
Violence is a disease.
跟癌癥一樣
Like cancer.
並且如同癌癥  我們希望有一天能控制住它
And like cancer, we hope to control it one day.
正是暴力讓我活到了今天
Violence is what kept me alive.
嚴格來說  你已經死了
Well technically, you're dead.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
我能得到什麼好處
What's in it for me?
一旦我的研究完成了
Once my research is complete,
就沒必要把你關在這裏了
there is no reason to keep you here.
我能過上以前的生活
I get my life back?
更好  你能擁有全新的生活
Better. A new one.
你不是餓了嗎
You are hungry.
你不知道他是什麼人  也不清楚他的本性
You don't know who he is, what he is.
他是個危險人物
He is a dangerous man.
再給他點時間  埃米爾
Give him little more time, Emir.
那傢伙可能會證明  他身上有高貴的血統
Man may prove that has some noble blood in him yet.
不如坐這裏吧  先生
How about here, sir?
菜單上有很多可選項  但我們推薦雞肉
It's an open menu, but we do recommend a chicken.
你需要什麼  林奇先生  菜單上有很多可選項
What can I get you, Mr. Lynch? It's an open menu,
但我們推薦雞肉
but we do recommend a chicken.
我要牛排
I'll steak.
給這位先驅來份牛排
Steak for the pioneer.
你是誰
Who are you?
他們都叫我穆薩
They call me Moussa.
但我的真名叫巴普蒂斯特  我已經死了200年了
But my name is Baptiste. I'm dead 200 years now.
巫毒大師
Voodoo poisoner.
我是無害的
I'm harmless.
他們都在觀察你
They're watching you.
等著看你是什麼樣的人  先驅
Waiting to see who you are, pioneer.
你見過他了嗎
Have you met him yet?
我們是伊甸蘋果最後的守護者  朋友
We are the last to protect the Apple, my friend.
你一旦做出錯誤的選擇
Pick the wrong choice,
就會把我們全部打入無限時空
you'll send us all to infinity.
這個
This...
屬於你
belongs to you.
你要帶領他們找到伊甸蘋果
You're going to lead them right to it.
不  我會把蘋果吃掉
No, I'm going to eat it.
到底怎麼回事
What the fuck is going on?
他必須再次進入阿尼姆斯
He has to go back in the Animus.
馬上
Now.
他需要休息一段時間  才能再次進入
He needs more time before he goes in again.
我們沒時間了
We don't have time.
為什麼
Why?
我不會拿他的生命冒險
I won't risk his life.
那我只好找其他人代勞了
I'll have to find someone else to do it.
到你了  猛男
You're up, slugger.
我瘋了
I'm crazy.
瘋狂想感覺如此孤寂
Crazy for feeling so lonely.
他們打算把他再次送進阿尼姆斯
They're getting him back in again.
我們應該在他背叛我們之前阻止他
We should stop him before he betrays us.
設置好中斷日期
Set the date for the six.
如果他的情況惡化  就把他拉出來
If his condition deteriorates, pull him out.
-你父親說...  -我不管他說過什麼
- You father... - I don't care what my father said.
我到底做錯了什麼
What in the world did I do?
-卡爾  聽我說  -我瘋狂嘗試...
- Cal, listen to me. - I'm crazy for trying...
聽我說  你必須跟阿圭拉保持合體狀態
Listen to me. You have to stay with Aguilar.
瘋狂想哭泣...
Crazy for crying...
脫離同步狀態可能會有危險
Staying in synch-void could be dangerous.
我瘋狂地愛著你...
And I'm crazy for loving you...
很快他們將進軍格拉納達
Soon they will march on Granada.
默罕默德蘇丹王很軟弱
Sultan Muhammad is weak.
他為了救王子
He'll surrender the Apple
肯定會交出蘋果  背叛信條
and betray the Creed to save the prince.
愛讓我們軟弱
The love makes us weak.
我願意犧牲自己的親骨肉
Gladly I'll sacrifice my flesh and blood,
換取信條永存
for survival of the Creed.
我今日若死  你無需為我落淚
When I die today, don't waste your tears for me.
主已給出指示
The Lord spoke.
他說
And he said:
"一個人若不住在我裏面
"If a man abide not in me
他就會被丟進火裏
he is cast into the fire
被焚燒殆盡"
and he is burned!"
數十年以來
For decades,
你們都活在因宗教紛爭
you have lived in the world torn apart
而分崩離析的世界
by religious discord.
但不久之後  多虧上帝
But soon, thanks to God
和宗教裁判所
and Inquisition
我們將徹底清除這種疾病
we will purge this disease!
在你們面前的罪人
The sinners before you,
企圖保護格拉納達的異教王子
sought to defend the heretic prince of Granada,
那裏是聖戰要攻下的最後一個異教徒據點
the last heathen stronghold in our holy war.
所以今天
So today,
在國王和王后的見證下
before our king and queen
我發誓  我們都將在上帝的聖火中
I swear we shall wash ourselves clean,
洗淨污穢
in the holy fire of God!
看啊
Behold...
上帝的旨意
God's will!
你將眼睜睜看著你的師父被燒死
You will watch your mentor burn
然後你也將受盡折磨而死
and then you will die the slowest.
將榮耀歸於未來
Give glory to the future.
而不是我們
Not to us.
他正在同步
He is synchronizing.
該死的異教徒
Damned heretics!
別讓他們跑了
Don't let them escape!
跳啊
Jump.
解除同步完成
Complete desynch.
放他下來
Get him down!
快叫醫護人員來
Call the medics!
沒事了  卡爾  堅持住  卡爾
Okay. It's okay. Cal, stay with me. Cal.
堅持住  沒事了  快點
Stay... It's okay. Hurry up!
沒事了  看著我
Okay. Okay. Look at me.
看著我
Look at me.
我的腿失去知覺了
I can't feel my legs.
身體麻痹只是暫時的
Paralysis is temporal.
壞消息是什麼
What's the bad news?
它引起了神經分裂  但我們把你治好了
It caused a neurological split but we got you through it.
這一次僥倖而已
This time.
我會死在這裏的  對吧
I'm gonna die in here, aren't I?
不
No.
如果你憑借你的自由意志進去  就不會死
Not if you go in there on your own free will.
我做不到
I can't do this.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
能找到伊甸蘋果的人只剩下你了
The Apple. You're the only one left who can find it.
我們能結束痛苦  卡爾
We can put an end to pain, Cal.
幫助所有人
For everyone.
你從哪裏找到的
Where did you get this?
我父親在你母親的兇殺現場找到的
My father recovered it from the scene of your mother's murder.
然後帶到這裏來保管
And brought it here for safekeeping.
保管
Safekeeping?
你們這是偷竊
You stole it.
這是你母親的項鏈  我想交給你
It's your mother's necklace. I wanted you to have it.
他為什麼會去那裏
Why was he there?
-去救她  -誰要害她
- To save her. - From whom?
-她的同僚  -那跟你有什麼關係
- Her own people. - What's that got to do with you?
刺客和聖殿騎士已經交戰了數個世紀
Assassins and Templars have been at war for centuries.
我希望能改變這局面
I aim to change that.
對哦  我忘了
That's right, I forgot.
我們的目的是根除暴力
We're here to combat aggression.
我不喜歡你的方式
I don't think I like your methods.
我是一個科學家
I am a scientist.
我來這裏是為了治好我暴力的一面
I'm here to be cured of violence.
但有誰能治好你呢
Who's gonna cure you?
我們是在餵養一頭野獸
We're feeding the beast.
我們在使他變得愈發強大
We're making him stronger.
我是萊肯博士
I am Dr Rikkin.
叫我亞倫吧
Alan.
我負責管理阿布斯泰戈
I look after things here in Abstergo.
你不喜歡讓外人插手  對吧
You like to keep things in the family, huh?
沒錯
Yes.
如果我們給你造成不適  很抱歉
I'm sorry if we caused you any discomfort.
有什麼需要我幫忙的嗎
Is there anything I can do?
讓我離開這裏怎麼樣
How about you let me out of here?
這件事我辦不到
That's something I can't manage.
我是來跟你做一筆交易的
I'm here to make a deal.
我們需要伊甸蘋果
We need the Apple.
也需要你幫我們找到它
And we need you to get it for us.
你在阿尼姆斯裏一直在解除同步
You've been desynching in the Animus.
請你不要再那樣做
We need you not to do that.
又要把我送進那台機器裏了嗎
Sending me back to the machine?
不  你已經讓我們看到我們需要看到的情形了
No, you've already shown us what we needed to see.
那你會釋放我們嗎
Will you let us free then?
你希望從那個新人身上得到什麼
What do you hope to gain from the newcomer?
能讓所有人都受益的東西
Something that'll benefit us all.
包括你  穆薩
You too, Moussa.
你對他們做了什麼
What have you done to them?
如果你用自己的意志
It's what happens
進行時空回溯  就會產生這種後果
if you don't enter in regression on your own volition.
你認識這個嗎
Do you recognize this?
這是刺客之刃
It's Assassin's blade.
你父親正是用這把刀
This is the actual one...
奪去了你母親的生命
your father used to take your mother's life.
他也在這裏  你知道嗎
He's here, you know?
一個母親的死亡  卡爾
Mother's death, Cal.
永遠不該讓她兒子看到
Not something a boy should ever be made to see.
這樣做不對
This is wrong.
是你讓我別無選擇
You left me no choice.
他一定要靠自己的自由意志進去  是你說的
He has to go in on his own free will, you said that.
-我只能去協商  -你是指操縱吧
- I had to negotiate. - You mean manipulate?
我向長老們承諾了我們會把伊甸蘋果送到倫敦
I assured the Elders we would have the Apple for London.
只剩下兩天時間了
That's in two days.
他不想知道自己的過去  也不想認識自己的父親
He doesn't want to know his past, or his father.
他想毀掉這兩樣東西
He wants to destroy them, both.
我們不是在製造怪物
We're not in the business of creating monsters.
我們沒有製造它們  也沒有毀掉它們
We neither created them nor destroyed them.
我們不過是將它們拋向自己必然的信念
We merely abandoned them to their own inexorable faith.
-你是你母親的孩子  -什麼意思
- You're your mother's son. - What does that mean?
你體內的血液不屬於你自己
Blood that flows through you is not your own.
而屬於信條
Belongs to the Creed.
你母親深知這一點
Your mother knew that.
她用死換來信條的傳承
She died so the Creed may live.
告訴我到底是怎麼回事
Remind me how, exactly!
你看到的事  是我幹的
What you saw, I did.
你殺了她
You murdered her.
我殺了她  總比讓那台機器弄死她要好
I took her life rather than have it stolen by that machine.
人因其崇高的使命而成長
Man grows with the greatness of his task.
我應該把你也殺了
I ought to have killed you.
我下不了手
I couldn't.
給你
Well, here.
拿著
Take it.
完成你30年前沒能做到的事
Do what you couldn't do 30 years ago.
如今刺客之刃已在你手中  卡爾
It's in your hands now, Cal.
這正是他們想要的結果
This is what they want.
殺了我
Spill my blood.
但千萬不要再進入阿尼姆斯
But do not go back in the Animus.
為什麼
Why?
伊甸蘋果當中蘊含著自由意志的基因密碼
The Apple contains the genetic code for free will.
他們會用來毀滅我們
They will use it to destroy us.
我一定會找到的
I'm gonna find it.
然後看著他們  毀掉你和你的信條
And watch them destroy you and your Creed.
信條是殺不死的
You can not kill the Creed.
它根植於你的血液中
It's in your blood.
伊甸蘋果就是一切
The Apple is everything.
你母親為了保護它犧牲了生命
Your mother died to protect it.
她當年別無選擇
She had no choice.
但我有
I do.
你要殺了信條
You're gonna kill the Creed!
帶我去阿尼姆斯
Take me to the Animus.
把我放進去
Put me in.
準備阿尼姆斯
Prepare the Animus.
自願回溯
Voluntary regression.
你知道殺手的名字是怎麼得來的
Do you know how the Assassins came to be named?
是根據阿拉伯詞語"哈薩辛"演變來的
From an Arabic word "Hashashin".
他們曾是社會的棄徒
They were society's outcasts.
他們會偷盜  冷血地殺人
Those who stole, who murdered in cold blood.
人們都嘲弄他們  叛黨  白癡  癮君子
People ridiculed them... Rebels, fools, drug addicts.
但其實他們很明智
But they were wise.
他們利用這種罵名  來隱藏自身對信條的忠貞
They used this reputation to hide the dedication to principles
甚至瞞過了最強大的敵人
beyond those of even their strongest enemies.
為此  我很欽佩他們
And for that I admire them.
但你不是其中的一員
But you're not one of those men.
對吧
Are you?
那就試試看吧
Let's find out.
開始回溯
Commencing regression.
這是我畢生的事業
This is my life's work.
這是我的生命
It's my life.
為了信條
For the Creed.
我們自身的生命
Our own lives...
重要的是  我們為後世留下什麼
What matters is what we leave behind.
蘇丹
Sultan...
把伊甸蘋果交出來
Surrender the Apple.
那些保護你的刺客都已經走了
Your Assassin protectors are gone.
信條已經完了
The Creed is finished.
我兒
My son.
這裏面是人類第一次違抗命令的種子
Here lies the seed of man's first disobedience,
是自由意志
of free will itself.
多虧了伊甸蘋果
Thanks to the Apple of Eden,
這已知的世界
the known world
將會被引入新紀元
shall be ushered into a new age.
一個和平的新紀元
One of peace,
在那裏  所有彼此敵對的人類
in which all the warring populations of mankind
將完全服從聖殿的統治
shall bow in perfect obedience to our one templar rule.
伊甸蘋果
The Apple.
交給他
Give it to him.
立刻
Now.
為了信條
For the Creed.
快走
Go!
原諒我
Forgive me.
已經結束了
It's over!
有刺客
Assassin!
信仰之躍
A leap of faith.
現在在哪兒
Where are we?
似乎是個軍事港口
It looks like a military port.
位於加的斯  帕洛斯德拉夫龍特拉
Kadiz, Palos de la Frontera.
刺客為此而死
The Assassins died for it.
用你的生命去保護它
Protect it with your life.
我是信條的朋友
I am a friend of the Creed.
帶入你的墳墓
Take it to your grave.
我發誓
I swear.
他們在說什麼  翻譯一下
What is it? Translation.
追尋著太陽的光芒
Following the light of the sun,
我將拋下這個舊世界
I shall leave this old world behind.
是克裏斯托弗·哥倫布
It's Christopher Columbus.
他的墳墓在哪裏
Where is he buried?
他的遺體被轉送回了西班牙
His remains were returned to Spain.
他的墳墓在塞維利亞大教堂裏
His tomb is in Seville Cathedral.
我們找到了
We found it.
全明星們  過來
Hey All Stars, come here.
挑一個
Pick one.
隨便選一個
Anyone.
-休息大廳發生襲擊事件  -封鎖阿尼姆斯
- Breach in common room. - Seal the Animus.
那是記憶嗎
Is it a memory?
不是
No.
快啊
Come on!
-傳輸裝置如何了  -準備就緒
- Transport? - Standing by.
保護好阿尼姆斯  肅清整個機構
Protect the Animus. Purge the facility.
我需要先把你救出去
I need to get you out of here first.
-不行  -我們必須走了  索菲婭
- No! - We have to leave, Sophia.
不
No!
不要
你不是一個人  卡爾
You are not alone, Cal.
你從來都不是
You never were.
-開門  -快
- Open... - Come on.
所有人都盲目追尋著真相時
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
-記住  -一切皆虛
- remember... - Nothing is true.
所有人都被道德或法律束縛時
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
-記住  -無事不允
- remember... - Everything is permitted.
我們在黑暗中侍奉光明
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們是刺客
We are Assassins.
現在要怎樣  先驅
What now, pioneer?
我們要戰鬥
We fight.
大人
Your Excellency.
榮譽將屬於你父親
The glory will go to your father.
但我們都知道是誰找到的
But we both know who found it.
屬於你的光輝時刻會到來的  孩子
Your time will come, my child.
倫敦  聖殿大廳
他們會為此把諾貝爾和平獎頒給你
They'll give you a Nobel peace prize for this.
你最好開始寫演講辭了
You better start writing your speech.
*-我看過你的演講辭了  -然後呢
- I've read yours. - And?
如果我們剷除了自由意志  就將刺客兄弟會消滅了
If we eradicate free will, we eradicate the Assassins.
他們就像是荼毒社會長達數個世紀的癌癥
A cancer that has menaced society for centuries.
那不是我的最佳作品  但意思都表達清楚了
It's not my best work, but it gets the point across.
我們一直在尋找解決辦法
We've been looking for solutions.
你解決了這個問題
You've eliminated the problem.
所以我的項目...
So my program...
第一次為這個社會帶來了秩序
Has brought order to society for the first time.
這一切都是我的功勞
I'm accountable for this.
已經算上你的功勞了
You've already been accounted for.
我們的成果都屬於長老會
Our work belongs to the Elders.
現在是他們最光榮的時刻
This is their finest hour.
你對我撒謊了
You lied to me.
我一直都知道
I've always known
在你心裏  科學排第一位  聖殿騎士團排第二
that in your heart you're a scientist first, templar second.
你最近的工作實在太令人嘆為觀止了
Your recent work has impressed as much
但那恰恰證實了我們的信仰
but it has confirmed our belief
也就是人類是無法獲得救贖的
that mankind cannot be redeemed.
所以你早就盤算好了一切
So you've thought of everything.
也不算吧  我的演講辭就沒想好
Not quite. My speech.
如果能加上你出色的開場白就更好了
It could do with one of your elegant openings.
現在我成了死神
Now I've become death,
世界的毀滅者
the destroyer of worlds.
不太確定我能否讓這一切實現
Not sure that I could make that work.
今晚  我很榮幸地向大家介紹
It is with great pleasure tonight that I introduce
我們古老騎士團的未來的構建者
the architect of our ancient order's future.
有請阿布斯泰戈基金會的總裁
Please welcome the CEO of Abstergo Foundation,
亞倫·萊肯博士
Dr. Alan Rikkin.
隨著伊甸蘋果被重新尋回
With the recovery of the Apple,
我們現在擁有了
we are now in possession
關於人類本能的完整基因地圖
of the complete genetic road map to humanity's instincts.
任何能導致獨立
Any impulse towards independence,
抗拒或反叛的衝動  都將被清除
resistance or rebellion will be crushed.
任何違背人類進步的體征
Any predisposition that might oppose our march of progress
現在都能被根除
can now be eradicated.
我只需大喊一聲  你就會沒命
All I have to do is shout.
我是來幫助你的
I'm here to help you.
你也是來幫助我的
And you're here to help me.
我幫不了你了
I can't help you anymore.
那麼那些偉大的計劃呢
What about all those great plans?
治癒暴力  攻擊性行為
Cure violence, combat aggression.
那是不可能的了
That's not going to happen.
是你開啟的這一切  索菲  你不能轉身離開
You've started this, Sophie. You don't get to walk away.
我們都知道接下來會怎樣
We both know what happens next.
並非所有東西都有資格活著
Not everything deserves to live.
我做不到
I can't do this.
不  你可以的
Yes, you can.
但我們不該將榮耀
But it is not to ourselves,
獻給自己  而是應該獻給未來
but to the future, that we must give glory.
一個沒有刺客信條的未來
A future purged of the Assassin's Creed!
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
這就是伊甸蘋果
the Apple of Eden.
是我幹的
I did this.
我會替長老會尋回寶物
I will retrieve the artifact for the Elders.
但我想把林奇留給自己
Lynch I want for me.
但我們不該將榮耀
It is not to ourselves,
獻給自己  而是應該獻給未來
but to the future, that we must give glory.